{
  "questions" : [ {
    "question" : "q1",
    "answers" : [ "answer1", "answer2", "answer3", "answer4" ],
    "correct_ans" : "2",
    "difficulty" : "1"
  }, {
    "question" : "q2",
    "answers" : [ "answer1", "answer2", "answer3", "answer4" ],
    "correct_ans" : "1",
    "difficulty" : "1"
  }, {
    "question" : "q3",
    "answers" : [ "answer1", "answer2", "answer3", "answer4" ],
    "correct_ans" : "3",
    "difficulty" : "1"
  }, {
    "question" : "q4",
    "answers" : [ "answer1", "answer2", "answer3", "answer4" ],
    "correct_ans" : "2",
    "difficulty" : "2"
  }, {
    "question" : "q5",
    "answers" : [ "answer1", "answer2", "answer3", "answer4" ],
    "correct_ans" : "1",
    "difficulty" : "2"
  }, {
    "question" : "q6",
    "answers" : [ "answer1", "answer2", "answer3", "answer4" ],
    "correct_ans" : "4",
    "difficulty" : "2"
  }, {
    "question" : "q7",
    "answers" : [ "answer1", "answer2", "answer3", "answer4" ],
    "correct_ans" : "3",
    "difficulty" : "3"
  }, {
    "question" : "q8",
    "answers" : [ "answer1", "answer2", "answer3", "answer4" ],
    "correct_ans" : "4",
    "difficulty" : "3"
  }, {
    "question" : "q9",
    "answers" : [ "answer1", "answer2", "answer3", "answer4" ],
    "correct_ans" : "2",
    "difficulty" : "3"
  }, {
    "question" : "sss",
    "answers" : null,
    "correct_ans" : null,
    "difficulty" : "1"
  }, {
    "question" : "lala",
    "answers" : [ "ansswerrrrr1", "tshuva2\t", "tshuva3", "sadsad" ],
    "correct_ans" : "1",
    "difficulty" : "1"
  }, {
    "question" : "dsasa",
    "answers" : [ "dsadsa", "sdadsa", "dsadsa", "sdasa" ],
    "correct_ans" : "2",
    "difficulty" : "2"
  }, {
    "question" : "asdsad",
    "answers" : [ "sadsad", "dsasda", "sdasda", "sdadsa" ],
    "correct_ans" : "2",
    "difficulty" : "2"
  }, {
    "question" : "zzzz",
    "answers" : [ "sadsad", "sadsadsad", "sadsad", "sadsad" ],
    "correct_ans" : "2",
    "difficulty" : "2"
  }, {
    "question" : "sadsad",
    "answers" : [ "sadsad", "sadsad", "dsadsa", "dsasad" ],
    "correct_ans" : "2",
    "difficulty" : "2"
  } ]
}